Hey sister uh I just felt led to say a
prayer for you um and just in the
spiritual warfare and the Demonic
attacks uh father God in the name of
Jesus Christ um we really nullify Lord
and dismantle and cancel and forcefully
oppose all satanic operations Maneuvers
and
manipulations subversions and strategies
oh Lord tactics and plots and plans and
P against the body of Christ and against
cat in Jesus Christ's name those P which
are designed to hinder Lord to prevent
to frustrate to foil Lord to deny or
delay God's original plans and purposes
for cat from their quick Swift and
Speedy manifestation taking place in a
correct time and season as Daniel 7:25
used to say and we dismantle and rebuke
all satanic alliances all satanic
confederations I bind in the name of the
Lord Jesus Christ arrest them Lord and
stop them by your holy spirit let every
covert and clandestine effort fail Lord
God cause the enemies to be routed out
but those that cannot be saved Lord we
pray that you would overtake them in
their own craft Y and Dev ways Lord let
them fall into their own pits that they
have dog for the righteous Let the Fire
of God devour them let them turn on and
consume one another and have them in
total confusion and derision Lord God we
loose the host of Heaven to war against
the host of darkness and bring an end to
all deceptive and secret and destructive
measures designed to
destroy cat's Channel and designed to
destroy the word of Truth getting out
and we overthrow spoken words Lord God
right now in the name of the Lord Jesus
Christ we bind enchantments now in the
name of the Lord Jesus Christ we bind
all divinations and spells and hexes and
vexes in Jesus Christ's Holy Name by the
blood of Jesus we bind curses witchcraft
prayers in jesus' name I bind and Every
Idle Word spoken contrary to God's
original plans and purposes um in Jesus
Christ's name we reverse right now the
curse is associated with all these
ceremonies and rituals utterances and
plans oh Lord God to stop the truth from
getting out Lord God in Jesus Christ's
name we take authority over these wicked
and evil lying Spirits father we humbly
ask you to reveal every hidden agenda
plan and cover up in um with those who
are around us and those that surround us
Lord regarding their attempts to
manipulate and their attempts to lead us
into destruction Lord and your righteous
seed and second Timothy Lord God used to
speak about just how
um that the last days Lord will be men
will be lovers of themselves and so Lord
send Divine powerful Angelic forces
against their diabolical plans to
frustrate and oh Lord we pray that you
expose the enemy so that the enemy's
plans will be dismantled Lord dispatch
Legions of Waring angels to enforce your
perfect will oh Lord God for uh the
Mandela effect and what this all means
and what it reveals about the timeline
and the time period that we're in your
time period Lord God that you have
orchestrated and allowed to come to pass
Lord release Your Divine strategies and
Revelation upon any righteous person
Lord in that is in any kind of authority
Lord God and arrest those as I said Lord
that operate in the spirit of Jezebel
and bile Lord and cause them to be
caught in their own lies and
conspiracies let them not be able to
resist the spirit of Truth or gain any
ground in the natural or spiritual realm
Lord God cause every spirit that is
released from their diabolical
assignment to be cast into the abyss
until which time they be cast into the
Lake of Fire Lord God please cause these
prayers and all future prayers to take
on the characteristics Lord of divine
projectiles in the realm of the spirit
so that they hit the bullseye Lord let
the laws that govern this prayer and all
spiritual warfare strategies and tactics
be binding by the blood of the Lord
Jesus Christ Lord God and beloved Holy
Savior Master Lord Jesus you are the
sacrifice Lord the lamb that was slain
before the foundation of the world Lord
before the foundation of the earth you
were seated at the right hand of the
father we honor your sacrifice on the
cross and celebrate your Resurrection
Lord and
Transfiguration that you volunteered
Lord out of your love for our Salvation
We Worship You Lord we exalt you and
magnify your name above every name Lord
you are the king of kings Lord you are
sovereign you are Supreme Over All you
are worthy of our praise and worthy of
the reward of your sufferings lord you
alone are worthy Lord we pledge our
faith and love to serve you alone and
forever Lord we the Bible used to say
when we resist the devil the devil will
flee from us you haven't given us a
spirit of fear but a power of love and a
and a sound mind Lord we come in the
authority given to us in Christ Jesus
Lord by the power of the Holy Spirit and
by the blood of the Lamb we place a
hedge of Waring angels with flaming
swords of fire around us continuously we
put on the whole armor of God we lift
our Shields of Faith to interlock
standing foot to to foot and shoulder
toosh shoulder a solid wall that cannot
be breached or penetrated we resist and
renounce Satan the God of this Earth We
rise to war in the spirit against any
witchcraft occult Maneuvers and devices
sent against your will in the body of
Christ we ask you to dispatch Legions
Lord Legions of Waring angels in full
battle array Lord fiery swords drawn to
enforce our petitions in intercessory
prayer route your enemy on all oh Lord
turn their hatred and anger and
accusations and conflict and arrogance
and wicked schemes upon themselves so
that they become caught in their own
snares and fall into their own pits that
they intended for cat Lord we nullify
and dismantle and cancel and oppose
every satanic operation scheme maneuver
and strategy I bind in the name of the
Lord Jesus Christ cause any secret plans
and agenda motivation of the enemy to be
revealed Lord for everyone to see Lord
God we decree and declare that what
these evil people meant for good you
will turn it around and use it for the
good of your people Lord we close every
evil portal Lord that has been opened we
Break Every curse and bind Every curse
hex spell Vex and enchantment stopping
the word from going out Lord stopping
the truth from going out we decree
spoken or unspoken Lord God any
enchantment against the body of Christ
and the truth from per ailing Lord we
bind against that which is against the
body of Christ and your intercessors
Lord by every witch and warlock Lord we
bind them and every Satanist we bind in
the name of Jesus and every Sorcerer And
voodoo priest we bind in the name of
Jesus every Shaman and bruhan and bruo
and suser and medium and coven and every
minion of the devil lord God working
iniquity and send it back upon their own
heads that they may repent and turn from
their evil ways Lord Jesus Reveal Your
Love to them Lord show them the truth
about who they're really serving Lord
and that their Eternal destination is
Hell Lord if they continue in the
present
pth open their minds and their eyes and
their ears to receive Supernatural
insight and knowledge to understand and
Care Lord about the truth of the Gospel
Lord bring them to Salvation Lord we
seal this Prayer by the blood of the
lamb and in the name of our Lord Jesus
Christ we pray in jesus' name oh Lord
everything that belongs bels to us we
ask for Giant Warrior Angels Lord and
whatever other kinds of angels are
necessary to be loosed now from Heaven
to S surround and protect us Lord as
your war club and weapons of war we
break down and undam and blow up all
walls of protection around all witches
warlocks Wizards Satanist and alike and
we break the power of all curses and
hexes and vexes and spells and charms
and fetishes and psychic prayers psychic
thought all witchcraft all sorcery all
magic all mind control all jinxes
potions and bewitchments death
destruction sickness pain and torment
and psychic power I bind now in the name
of Jesus Christ Let There Be freedom for
God's people when the enemy comes in
like a flood the spirit of the Lord
would raise a standard against him all
psychic Warfare all prayer chains and
everything else being sent against the
body of Christ and the innocent and our
families ways and that you would return
it to the demons and devils and the evil
entities and Fallen Angels right now
Sevenfold and we bind it to them by the
blood of Jesus father we pray that these
lost souls will find the light of your
son Jesus Christ that are that their own
snares and traps have now been set
against themselves Lord and in the name
of Jesus Christ of Nazareth we now loose
them from all the mind control of Satan
Lord father we also ask that you bind
the Holy Spirit to their hearts as your
guide your son Jesus Christ so they may
be set free from the bondages of Satan
in Jesus Christ's name I pray amen God
bless you Sister I pray that this prayer
uh can be fruitful and manifest the
protection and that also that you would
be delivered from unreasonable and
wicked men for Not all men have faith I
love you sister God bless